ebookslab.info 2009-03-10

# Privacy Policy | Download Free Ebooks Collection

Ebookslab. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site:

**IP Address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We may also track IP addresses for purposes of enrollment and/or subscription.

**Information Collection**

We are the sole owner of the information collected on Ebookslab.info. We collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site, i.e. for membership registration, paid subscription publications and products or services.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Information Sharing**

**Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties**  
We will never sell or give away your personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists, or anything of that nature, without your permission. We stands firmly against any transfer of personal information for reasons of building the contact lists of third parties.

**Business Transition Exception**  
In the event we goes through a business transition, such as a merger, or being acquired by another company, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. We also use third party providers to accept credit cards and checks through Paysystems, 1Shoppingcart.com, Clickbank, and 2Checkout.com (each keeps your personal information separate, secure and confidential.) 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**"Cookies"**

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We also use cookies for tracking and properly crediting affiliates in our Affiliate Program (using services like [Clickbank.com](http://www.clickbank.com/)).

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as their name and email address), unique identifiers (such as their Affiliate ID), and financial information (such as their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration in eBooks N' Bytes Affiliate Program and to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as Affiliate IDs) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system.

**Children**

We does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe our Publishers has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. We are not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them.

We works hard to ensure that the information contained on our web pages is accurate, relevant and of the high quality that our visitors have come to expect.

We are aware of software that exists which will create external links from our content to what they consider to be related material, which other companies have paid to have shown. We are not responsible for the quality of this software or the nature of the material that it links to

We emphasize that we are strictly against this form of unmoderated and unregulated link advertising and strictly prohibit its use within our site content.

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  * email manzaa@mzworld.com

We reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
